const qBank = [
  {
    question: 'Colic is a problem for horses because?',
    answers: ['They cannot burp', 'They cannot regurgitate', 'Both'],
    correct: 'Both',
    questionId: '099099',
  },
  {
    question: 'An intact male horse over two years old is called a ?',
    answers: ['Stud', 'Stallion', 'Both'],
    correct: 'Both',
    questionId: '183452',
  },
  {
    question: 'A well-cared-for horse can live ?',
    answers: ['10 years at most', 'More than 30 years', 'Around 15 years'],
    correct: 'More than 30 years',
    questionId: '267908',
  },
  {
    question: 'The most popular breed of horse is the ?',
    answers: ['Arabian', 'Quarter Horse', 'Thoroughbred'],
    correct: 'Quarter Horse',
    questionId: '333247',
  },
  {
    question: 'Behaviorally, horses most prefer to ?',
    answers: ['Live in a group', 'Live with a friend', 'Go it alone'],
    correct: 'Live in a group',
    questionId: '496293',
  },
  {
    question: 'WThe original horse was called ?',
    answers: ['Eohippus', 'Phorusrhacos', 'Equisaurus'],
    correct: 'Eohippus',
    questionId: '588909',
  },
  {
    question: 'Full-sized horses and standard ponies are measured in ?',
    answers: ['Inches', 'Centimeters', 'Hands'],
    correct: 'Hands',
    questionId: '648452',
  },
  {
    question: 'A female horse over two years old is called a?',
    answers: ['Sow', 'Mare', 'Doe'],
    correct: 'Mare',
    questionId: '786649',
  },
  {
    question: 'Horses usually sleep?',
    answers: ['Lying down', 'Standing up', 'With one eye open'],
    correct: 'Standing up',
    questionId: '839754',
  },
  {
    question:
      'When you are buying a horse, the best way to determine its age by?',
    answers: [
      'Asking the seller',
      'Having a veterinarian examine the horse',
      'Looking at its teeth',
    ],
    correct: 'Having a veterinarian examine the horse',
    questionId: '98390',
  },
  {
    question: 'Miniature horses are measured in?',
    answers: ['Inches or centimeters', 'Hands or feet', 'Meters'],
    correct: 'Inches or centimeters',
    questionId: '1071006',
  },
  {
    question: 'A newborn horse of either gender is called a?',
    answers: ['Pup', 'Foal', 'Calf'],
    correct: 'Foal',
    questionId: '1174154',
  },
  {
    question: 'Horses, ponies, donkeys, mules and zebras are all?',
    answers: ['Bovines', 'Equines', 'Ruminants'],
    correct: 'Equines',
    questionId: '1226535',
  },
  {
    question:
      'According to art in Egyptian pyramids, horses have been domesticated for?',
    answers: ['A thousand years', ' Centuries', 'Three thousand years'],
    correct: 'Three thousand years',
    questionId: '1310938',
  },
  {
    question: 'Arabian horses have an unusual physique because?',
    answers: [
      'They are exceptionally large',
      'They have one less set of ribs than other horses',
      'They are very strong',
    ],
    correct: 'They have one less set of ribs than other horses',
    questionId: '1436873',
  },
  {
    question: ' A weaned female foal is called a?',
    answers: ['Weanling', 'Filly', 'Both'],
    correct: 'Both',
    questionId: '1515110',
  },
  {
    question: 'The withers is the?',
    answers: [
      ' Highest point of a horse’s back',
      'A horse’s ankle',
      'The area between a horse’s ears',
    ],
    correct: ' Highest point of a horse’s back',
    questionId: '1642728',
  },
  {
    question:
      'Crosses between different types of equines produce hybrids that are usually? ',
    answers: ['Sterile', 'Strong', 'Both'],
    correct: 'Both',
    questionId: '1747256',
  },
  {
    question: 'Pound-for-pound, the strongest equine is the?',
    answers: ['Draft horse', 'Shetland pony', 'Donkey'],
    correct: 'Donkey',
    questionId: '1822532',
  },
  {
    question: 'Gray horses are usually born?',
    answers: ['Gray', 'A darker color', 'White'],
    correct: 'A darker color',
    questionId: '195075',
  },
  {
    question: 'The mother of a horse is called its ?',
    answers: ['Mom', 'Mater', 'Dam'],
    correct: 'Dam',
    questionId: '2019778',
  },
  {
    question: 'Equines are ?',
    answers: ['Omnivores', 'Herbivores', 'Carnivores'],
    correct: 'Herbivores',
    questionId: '2134343',
  },
  {
    question: 'Horses’ evolutionary ancestors include ?',
    answers: ['Hippopotamus', 'Goats and deer', 'None of the above'],
    correct: 'None of the above',
    questionId: '2210799',
  },
  {
    question: 'A female horse used entirely for breeding is called a ?',
    answers: ['Breeder', 'Interbreed', 'Brood mare'],
    correct: 'Brood mare',
    questionId: '2379831',
  },
  {
    question: 'A neutered male horse over two years old is called a ?',
    answers: ['Gelding', 'Steer', 'Eunuch'],
    correct: 'Gelding',
    questionId: '2426418',
  },
  {
    question: 'Well-trained ponies are good for?',
    answers: [
      'Teaching children to ride',
      'Pulling carts and sleighs',
      'All of the above',
    ],
    correct: 'All of the above',
    questionId: '2510086',
  },
  {
    question: 'An “easy-keeper” ?',
    answers: ['Needs less food to stay fit', 'Is easy to handle', 'Is lazy'],
    correct: 'Needs less food to stay fit',
    questionId: '2685745',
  },
  {
    question: 'The father of a horse is called its ?',
    answers: ['Dad', 'Pater', 'Sire'],
    correct: 'Sire',
    questionId: '2796884',
  },
  {
    question: 'A healthy ____ usually has the longest, thickest mane and tail.',
    answers: ['Donkey', 'Thoroughbred', 'Pony'],
    correct: 'Pony',
    questionId: '2838900',
  },
  {
    question: 'A cross between a donkey and a zebra is called a?',
    answers: ['Zonkey', 'Zedonk', ' Either'],
    correct: 'Either',
    questionId: '298060',
  },
  {
    question: 'The animal that was first domesticated is the?',
    answers: ['Cat', 'Horse', 'Dog'],
    correct: 'Dog',
    questionId: '3096579',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of these equines generally lives longer?',
    answers: ['Pony', 'Draft Horse', 'Donkey'],
    correct: 'Donkey',
    questionId: '3182461',
  },
  {
    question: 'How old is a 28 year old horse in human years?',
    answers: ['40 years', '60 years', '80 years'],
    correct: '80 years',
    questionId: '3239112',
  },

  {
    question:
      'Can deworming your horse on a regular basis help prevent colic? ',
    answers: ['Yes', 'No', 'None'],
    correct: 'Yes',
    questionId: '3318503',
  },
  {
    question:
      'According to recent studies, what percentage of saddles do not fit the horse they are used on?"',
    answers: ['10-15%', '20-25%', '75% or more'],
    correct: '75% or more',
    questionId: '3410327',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the resting heart rate for the average adult horse?',
    answers: [
      '30-40 beats per minute',
      '50-60 beats per minute',
      '70-80 beats per minute',
    ],
    correct: '30-40 beats per minute',
    questionId: '3542596',
  },
  {
    question:
      'If your horse has asymmetrical shoulders (meaning shoulders that are not the same size and shape), should you use saddle pad shims in:”',
    answers: [
      'Both sides of your saddle pad',
      'Only the side with the larger, more developed shoulder',
      'Only the side with the small, less developed shoulder',
    ],
    correct: 'Only the side with the small, less developed shoulder',
    questionId: '3667517',
  },
  {
    question: ' How tight should your horse’s noseband be if you use one?',
    answers: [
      'One finger should fit between the noseband leather and horses nose',
      'Two fingers should fit between the noseband leather and the horses nose',
      ' It depends on how hot the horse is.',
      'Kiwi Food Cut',
    ],
    correct:
      'Two fingers should fit between the noseband leather and the horses nose',
    questionId: '3791672',
  },

  {
    question:
      'Horses usually live for around 20 to 25 years but a horse called Old Billy holds theworld record for being the oldest horse that has ever lived. How old was he when he died ?',
    answers: [' 52 years old', '62 years old', '72 years old'],
    correct: '62 years old',
    questionId: '3893585',
  },
  {
    question:
      'How many horses do the New York City Police Department have to assist officerswith their official duties across the streets and parks of New York?',
    answers: ['about 10', 'about 100', 'about 1000'],
    correct: 'about 100',
    questionId: '3913430',
  },
  {
    question:
      'What is the typical average speed of a horse when it is galloping?',
    answers: ['25 to 30 mph  ', '35 to 40 mph ', '45 to 50 mph'],
    correct: '25 to 30 mph',
    questionId: '4049121',
  },
  {
    question:
      'What is the common unit of measurement for measuring a horse height?',
    answers: ['centimetres', 'feet', 'hands'],
    correct: 'hands',
    questionId: '4150746',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is a common way of assessing a horses age?',
    answers: [
      'examining its hooves',
      'examining its mane',
      'examining its teeth',
    ],
    correct: 'examining its teeth',
    questionId: '4235063',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the correct name for a young female horse?',
    answers: ['filly', 'mare', 'colt'],
    correct: 'Libra',
    questionId: '4321002',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the correct name for anadult female horse?',
    answers: ['filly', 'mare', 'colt'],
    correct: 'mare',
    questionId: '4442286',
  },
  {
    question: 'A baby horse is born with no teeth.',
    answers: ['Yes', 'No', 'None Of the Above'],
    correct: 'Yes',
    questionId: '4564430',
  },
  {
    question: 'When is it believed that horses were first domesticated?',
    answers: [
      'about 2000 years ago  ',
      'about 4000 years ago',
      'about 6000 years ago',
    ],
    correct: 'about 6000 years ago',
    questionId: '4630606',
  },
  {
    question:
      'Which of the following famous racehorses does not have a biopic?',
    answers: ['Ruffian', 'War Admiral', 'Secretariat'],
    correct: 'War Admiral',
    questionId: '4795960',
  },
  {
    question:
      'WA mustang known as Comanche was the mount of which well-known commander?',
    answers: ['George Custer', 'Catherine the Great', 'Genghis Khan'],
    correct: 'George Custer',
    questionId: '4811162',
  },
  {
    question:
      'What’s the name of a mid-20th-century TV show that featured a talking horse?',
    answers: ['Three’s Company', 'Mr. Ed', 'Rocky and Bullwinkle'],
    correct: "Arby's",
    questionId: '4982981',
  },
];

export default (n = 5) =>
  Promise.resolve(qBank.sort(() => 0.5 - Math.random()).slice(0, n));
